

About Me

This is Mehedi Hassan from at Dhaka in Bangladesh. I'm a professional Flutter developer. I have been working since 2022 in this platform. Now I able to build any type of application.

Expertise Skill

- Auto Mobiles
- Flutter
- Basic Firebase
- Basic Dart, C, Java etc.
- Chatting
- API integration
- State Management (GetX, Provider)

Contact Me

+8801639483485

hassandevbd@gmail.com Shahibag, Savar Dhaka LinkedIn GitHub

MD. Mehedi Hassan

Flutter Developer

Education

2019-2020 (HSC)Government Debendra College

2021-Present (B.Sc. in CSE)
Department of Computer
Science and engineering, <u>City</u>
<u>University</u>

Work Experience

- Junior Flutter DeveloperPilot Bazar | 2023-2024
 - Chatting Application
 - API Integration
 - UI Design
 - Upload app on Play Store App Link

Junior Flutter Developer

Guideasy Global Limited | 2023-2024

- API Integration
- UI Design